* Initialization of parameter/Limit value recommended when changing Joint

■ Common
[Restriction]: A - B | range (movement: space distance / rotation: shaft rotation frequency)

 A<B | Limited by range
 A=B | Lock with specified value (Complete locking is impossible due to distance difference from rigid body, etc.)
 A>B | No limit (free)

■ Spring attached 6DOF
[Spring]: coefficient value used in spring calculation

■ ConeTwist
[Restriction / Parameter]
dp_x: damping (0) - If fixThresh (1) | 0 - 0, the physical calculation may be corrupted
dp_z: (Fixed) Motor enabled (0: OFF / 1: ON) - Motor impulse value

Rotation: Rotation range around X / Y / Z axis (+ - shared) | x: 60 -> - 60 to +60

* To be precise, with respect to the axial direction (initial position and X axis reference)
 X: Torsion direction
 Y: Expansion of rotation range - Horizontal (vertical)
 Z: Expansion of rotation range - Vertical (horizontal)
(Standard axis orientation can be easily set from [Axial orientation] to Fixed direction) (+ - XYZ))

[Parameter / Motor angle]
fc: softness, biasFactor, relaxationFactor | Joint parameter (standard: 1 / 0.3 / 1)
MtA: Fixed angle when motor is enabled? Angle (X / Y / Z)

* (Fixed) Behavior of motor (problem)
· Z of the rotation range is required to be 60 (degrees) or more (In the absence of rotation, the rotation range is broken)
· Fixed at specified angle (specification?)

For continued rotation purpose, use of the motor at Hinge below is recommended

■ Slider
The movement / rotation axis is based on the "X axis" direction reference (the axial direction corresponds to the Joint orientation change)
* Easy setting from [Axial direction] to fixed direction (+ - XYZ)

[motor]
Move / Rotate (common): Motor valid (0: OFF / 1: ON), Motor speed, Motor maximum force

* The rotation control by Slider does not operate correctly depending on the range

■ Hinge
The rotation axis is based on the "Z axis" direction reference (the axial direction corresponds to the Joint orientation change)
* Easy setting from [Axial direction] to fixed direction (+ - XYZ)

[Parameter / motor]
fc: softness, biasFactor, relaxationFactor | Joint parameter (standard: 0.9 / 0.3 / 1)
Rotation: Rotating motor enabled (0: OFF / 1: ON), Motor speed, Motor maximum force

* Continuous rotation is possible when the motor is used with the rotation limit set to free (-180 to +180 / 1 to 0, etc.)
